export default data12 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "When is St George’s day?",
        options: ["7th March", "30th November", "1st March", "23rd April"],
        correct_option: "23rd April"
    },
     {
        id: "q2",
        question: "Which is the largest National Park in England?",
        options: ["Snowdonia", "Trossachs National Park", "The Giant’s Causeway", "The Lake District"],
        correct_option: "The Lake District"
    },
     {
        id: "q3",
        question: "Boudicca, was a tribal leader who fought against which foreign invaders?",
        options: ["The Normands", "The Vikings", "The Anglo-Saxons", "The Romans"],
        correct_option: "The Romans"
    },
     {
        id: "q4",
        question: "Which of the following poems is about a group of people going on a pilgrimage?",
        options: ["The Canterbury Tales", "All the world’s a stage", "A Midsummer Night’s dream", "Great Expectations"],
        correct_option: "The Canterbury Tales"
    },
     {
        id: "q5",
        question: "How are public holidays called?",
        options: ["Bank Holidays", "Workers Holidays", "Business Holidays", "Summer Holidays"],
        correct_option: "Bank Holidays"
    },
     {
        id: "q6",
        question: "How did Charles II manage to escape to Europe after his defeat in the Civil War?",
        options: ["Hiding in a farmer's house", "Riding a horse", "Hiding in an oak tree", "Swimming"],
        correct_option: "Hiding in an oak tree"
    },
     {
        id: "q7",
        question: "Who defeated the Vikings?",
        options: ["Harold", "Edward I of England", "King Arthur", "King Alfred the Great"],
        correct_option: "King Alfred the Great"
    },
     {
        id: "q8",
        question: "Where do Beefeaters serve as tour guides?",
        options: ["The Houses of the Parliament", "The Tower of London", "The O2", "The Big Ben"],
        correct_option: "The Tower of London"
    },
     {
        id: "q9",
        question: "During the rebellion of the clans in Scotland, Bonnie Prince Charlie was supported by clansmen from which Scottish region?",
        options: ["Glasgow", "Galloway", "Highlands", "Edinburgh"],
        correct_option: "Highlands"
    },
     {
        id: "q10",
        question: "What religion did Elizabeth I follow?",
        options: ["She was a Protestant", "She was a Catholic"],
        correct_option: "She was a Protestant"
    },
     {
        id: "q11",
        question: "Who became famous for his tramp character in silent movies?",
        options: ["Sir Rex Harrison", "David Niven", "Richard Burton", "Charlie Chaplin"],
        correct_option: "Charlie Chaplin"
    },
     {
        id: "q12",
        question: "Which armed force was used in the Battle of Britain?",
        options: ["The Royal Navy", "The Police Force", "The Naval Service", "The Royal Air Force"],
        correct_option: "The Royal Air Force"
    },
     {
        id: "q13",
        question: "In the UK, you have to be 21 years old to be able to vote in a general election.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q14",
        question: "Which of the following poets was inspired by nature?",
        options: ["John Masefield", "Wilfred Owen", "Siegfried Sassoon", "William Wordsworth"],
        correct_option: "William Wordsworth"
    },
     {
        id: "q15",
        question: "Against which country did Britain fight at the Battle of Waterloo?",
        options: ["Germany", "Italy", "France", "Spain"],
        correct_option: "France"
    },
     {
        id: "q16",
        question: "Who was William Wilberforce?",
        options: ["A poet", "A sportsman", "A politician", "A musician"],
        correct_option: "A politician"
    },
     {
        id: "q17",
        question: "Who is the spiritual leader of the Church of England?",
        options: ["The Archbishop of Canterbury", "The Archbishop of London", "The Archbishop of Birmingham", "The Archbishop of Manchester"],
        correct_option: "The Archbishop of Canterbury"
    },
     {
        id: "q18",
        question: "James I was King of which country before becoming King of England?",
        options: ["Wales", "Ireland", "France", "Scotland"],
        correct_option: "Scotland"
    },
     {
        id: "q19",
        question: "Which country sent a fleet of ships to England in 1588?",
        options: ["France", "Germany", "Spain", "Italy"],
        correct_option: "Spain"
    },
     {
        id: "q20",
        question: "Where is the National Horseracing Museum located?",
        options: ["Edinburgh, Scotland", "Newmarket, Suffolk", "St Andrews, Scotland", "Aintree near Liverpool"],
        correct_option: "Newmarket, Suffolk"
    },
     {
        id: "q21",
        question: "Which of the following castles is located in Scotland?",
        options: ["Crathes Castle", "Caernarfon Castle", "Bodiam Castle", "Powis Castle"],
        correct_option: "Crathes Castle"
    },
     {
        id: "q22",
        question: "Who was a famous Art Deco ceramic designer?",
        options: ["Alexander McQueen", "Thomas Chippendale", "Clarice Cliff", "Mary Quant"],
        correct_option: "Clarice Cliff"
    },
     {
        id: "q23",
        question: "Each MP represents a parliamentary constituency, which is a small area of the country:",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
     {
        id: "q24",
        question: "Who led the establishment of the National Health System (NHS) in 1948?",
        options: ["Aneurin (Nye) Bevan", "Harold Macmillan", "Clement Attlee", "William Beveridge"],
        correct_option: "Aneurin (Nye) Bevan"
    },
    
]